http://rinkworks.com/privacy/

Main      Site Guide
Privacy Policy
RinkWorks respects the privacy and confidentially of its associates
and readers.
Below is our policy regarding the privacy of Internet users.
RinkWorks does not acquire or collect any
personal information about you for any reasons other than internal use, except
where explicitly indicated.
Any and all personal information collected for internal use will
be treated confidentially; it will not be given out, nor will it be used for
any purpose other than the operation of the RinkWorks site.
(For
example, some of our online features require registration to participate.
If
there is a technical problem, or a question we have concerning your use of
the feature, we will use your email address, as submitted to us upon
registration, to contact you about these matters.
Your email address will
not, however, be sold or given out to anyone.)
RinkWorks does,
however, accrue anonymous information which is specific to its readers'
browsing habits on RinkWorks.
This information is anonymous; it
does not contain personal details, although it does contain non-personally
identifying details, including, but not limited to, your IP address and the
browser you are using.
This information is obtained solely for the purpose of
tracking traffic flow patterns through the RinkWorks site and
measuring levels of interest and accessibility in different areas of
RinkWorks.
An addendum to the above, RinkWorks does, in some explicitly
documented instances, collect voluntarily-supplied personal information,
including but not limited to the Demographic
Survey, which is used to collect information about the types of
visitors RinkWorks receives, is voluntary, and is always anonymous.
In this and all other cases where RinkWorks asks for personal
information, it will be kept strictly confidential and used only for the
purposes expressed when it is asked for.
RinkWorks uses third-party
advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site.
These
companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address,
email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web
sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest
to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know
your choices about not having this information used by these companies,
click here.
These companies may also temporarily store some code within
your browser that allows the advertising agencies we work with to respond
properly to the ads that are delivered.
These codes are commonly known as
"cookies."
The cookies served in conjunction with the advertising are not
the doing, nor the responsibility of RinkWorks.
For more information please see the following details associated with a
subset of the advertising agencies we work with:
Concerning Exponential Interactiv:
Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.
Concerning ValueClick/Fastclick:
"We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our web site
for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement
'click-throughs,' and/or other activities on our web site. Where authorized by
us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring
technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors.
No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any
party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information
is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at
http://media.valueclick.com/privacy_consumer.shtml.
This web site contains links to other sites.
This privacy policy is for the sole use and purpose of RinkWorks
and does not cover the sites RinkWorks links to.
Please be aware
that RinkWorks is not responsible for the privacy practices of
such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy practices of each and
every web site that collects your personal information.
This site makes public forums available to
you, including, but not limited to, the
Message Forum
and RinkChat.
Please be aware,
whenever you post personal information online, through the Message
Forum, RinkChat, or other public online area, that this
information can be collected and used by others.
RinkWorks
assumes any and all information posted to these public areas as intended
for public disclosure.
RinkWorks takes reasonable security
measures to protect the loss, inappropriate disclosure, and misuse of
the information under our control.
However, should a breach in security
occur and information stolen or altered by anyone, RinkWorks
cannot be held responsible for this loss or theft.
Back to RinkWorks.
